Hello everyone! I'm Seina Saito from the Equal Department.
I'm Shoko Takioki.
I'm Ohabara.
I'm Risa Otoshima.
Hello! Today's project is
Equal Club Year-End Party
It's okay party
Yes, we did it in September.
You know the 6th anniversary YouTube live performance we did in September?
Bomberman of that
We all had a showdown.
And I won!
I won!
The prize was a six-person
A big shabu-shabu for 6 people!
So today, we're going to eat it together.
Are you sure?
And it's for 6 people!
That's a lot of food!
Wow!
Are you sure it's okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
No leftovers.
Oh, my God!
I'm glad you guys are eating.
I have the ingredients right here. Here are the ingredients.
One to arrange the sea bream nicely.
And one to cut the vegetables.
I don't know.
Have you guys ever chopped vegetables before?
Wait a minute.
Have you ever cut vegetables?
Like in home economics?
If Shoko's still here.
I might be able to do it.
What do you think?
Have you ever cut vegetables?
Yes, I have.
I have, but I'm more afraid of the end.
Afraid of the end?
I don't know.
It's too short.
Oh, yeah. Once you've made up your mind.
I'm going to do something really dangerous.
Dangerous.
There you go.
Shall we cut the vegetables?
Oh, okay.
Me and Shoko will cut the vegetables.
Yes, please.
You two? The two of us?
I'll do my best to serve it.
Let's do our best.
Let's do it!
Let's do it.
Okay, I'd like to start serving.
Okay!
First of all, let's open it!
Oh, please.
I'll give it a try.
What's this? Is that an octopus?
A tie?
Octopus. Octopus.
You can do octopus, too?
You can do octopus, too.
Aahhh!
Wow!
A tie! A tie!
Oh, my gosh, it's huge!
Now, let's serve it...what should we do?
What should we do with it?
Circle?
Oh!
It's pretty short. I'm torn.
No, you didn't. No.
You want me to open it for you?
I'll give it a shot.
Like this?
That's it.
It's ripped!
It's ripped off.
But if you put them on top of each other...
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Peketan////
Wait, this is it, this is the one that separated.
Can you help me?
Can we blend them together?
Not here? Here.
We'll blend them in.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's okay. I'll let it sink in.
Wait a minute.
Let's just...
Let's put it on top.
Then we'll cut the vegetables too.
I'd like to cut them. I'd like to cut it off.
Let's do it.
Where to start?
Start with potherb mustard
Let's start with the big one.
That's about right.
That's good, right?
Green onion
It's getting better and better.
I like this one.
Let's prepare the soup stock.
Please do.
Negi should be diagonal, right?
Diagonal is good.
How about this?
How about you?
Hold on.
There's a little bit of this other thing coming up.
It's like a puzzle.
Oh, my God.
I'm playing a puzzle game right now.
Are you playing the puzzle game?
Are you playing a puzzle game?
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Oh, okay. Eh, okay.
It's fine.
Isn't it beautiful?
You're gonna have to stop looking around here for a second.
It's nice.
The rest of it looks good.
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
I knew it might be used for a thumbnail, so here.
I knew it! For the thumbnail!
Wow, great.
Wow, it's beautiful.
I have to make it look good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
It's frozen again.
It's...
It's frozen.
Congratulations.
Wait a minute.
Oh, shit.
Can you go?
If you don't loosen it, it'll tear again.
My hands are so cold.
I'm shoveling snow. I'm shoveling snow.
Oh, my God.
Shoveling snow.
I'm gonna rip it all up.
Can you cut this?
Do you have scissors or something?
You don't have to cut it, do you?
You don't have to cut it.
I can't cut it.
I couldn't cut it.
I'll put an egg in it.
Two eggs?
I don't know.
Do you think it's okay?
One more.
Ingestion line
Three.
Change.
IKE (Japanese rice wine)
Cold.
Cold?
Wait for it to boil.
wait
Wait
Only wait Wait and see.
Oh, my God.
It smells so good.
Hey, Tashin...
It's nice when they're working together.
That's good to know.
You're not hanging up?
I don't know.
Let's make them into flowers.
Like this.
Flowers.
Can you do it?
Let's make flowers.
Which one do you want?
Like roses, like this.
It's nice, isn't it? There you go.
It looks good.
How about this one?
It's good.
He says it's good.
And this one?
It's good.
Like this.
And this one.
That's good.
That's good. It looks good.
It's done.
That was fast.
First time maybe.
Hey, it's my first time.
I've never done this before.
I'm glad.
I'm hungry
Beautiful.
Here.
Oh, no, no, no
Oh, oh, oh,
here
Here you go.
Beautiful.
Beautiful
Beautiful lettuce
Stuffed.
Finished cutting
Yay, that was quick!
Shook cut it for me.
He did a good job.
This one, too.
Me too.
What do you think? What do you think?
I don't know.
I'll say goodbye for now.
But it looks good.
It's cottony.
It's normal.
It's better that way.
It's supposed to taste better.
What do you think?
Why not?
It's octopusy.
Octopus? That's pretty octopusy.
Oh, I don't think it's alive.
But it's pretty bad.
It's a little...
That, too.
It's like a jar!
It's like a pressure point.
It's like it's stuck.
What are you doing?
Oh, but...
There.
The nose.
I can't tell if it's a Thai or an octopus.
It's still there.
I'm still here. I'm still here.
My eyes went crazy.
I touched an octopus raw for the first time.
The octopus is iconic.
Oh, my God.
But isn't it nice? There you go.
Ready?
It's done.
Isn't it pretty good?
Surprisingly good.
Here, too.
I layered them so many times.
It's like a flower with a lot of volume.
The octopus in the middle is surprising.
The octopus in the middle is a nice accent.
It's gone.
It looks good.
Yay!
Okay, we're all set.
Let the Equal Club 5-Year Anniversary Mass Party begin!
Let's get in!
What kind of food should we put in?
A grilled top sounds delicious!
One-pot dish. Hot pot.
I read that you can put a Thai in there for a second.
It falls apart.
Like grilled fish?
It's not like grilled fish.
So, it's the five-year anniversary party.
Let's do the second one of the year.
2023. That's great.
Let's take a tour of love's appearance and head.
How's your consciousness?
It was so automatic.
We made a movie.
I hope you guys saw it.
I'm sure they saw it.
I had a blast in 4DX.
It was my first time in 4DX.
I screamed so hard.
I'm gonna be gone all summer.
I'm not going to turn it off all summer.
There was a cool event.
It's gonna be good if you're not here.
You're here.
You should go.
The one in the middle?
Which one?
The octopus or the Thai one? Is it an octopus or a Thai?
I knew you wouldn't do it.
You're not gonna do it.
Can you go?
I'll go.
Okay.
Yeah?
Oh, it's really that one.
Oh, it's changing color!
It's getting darker.
Is that good?
It's getting softer.
It's not burned.
Not burned.
Oh, that's good.
Thank you.
Oh, it's delicious.
Bon appétit.
Hey!
Is it good?
Yum!
Yum! Yummy?
Oh, my God!
It's so good! It's so good!
Because I bought a real man.
Thank you so much for doing it just in time.
Shab-shab.
Shove, shove, shove.
It's good, right?
Is it good?
Bon appétit.
First pie shabu shabu.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's good.
Soft. It's my first time.
Soft. Happy.
I'm gonna put it on.
You always do.
Yay, it's soft.
It's so soft, it's making me all shiny.
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum.
It's good, isn't it?
It's delicious.
Soft!
It's so soft!
Soft and fluffy!
Oh, my gosh!
Taste like hot pot? Taste like hot pot?
Yeah.
Dashi?
You just put broth in it.
It's kind of nice.
Yeah!
It'll go well with dessert.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's good! Delicious!
Delicious mushrooms!
Delicious bamboo shoots!
Can I eat it?
Go ahead!
Is it growing?
It's growing!
It's working!
Is this okay?
Yes!
Rikko, take the challenge!
It's so chewy!
Hey! Tuna is done, right?
It's so elastic!
Is it okay?
Is it gonna be okay? Can we go?
I wasn't talking about this year.
I'm too serious about eating.
We're only through the summer.
Three singles this year.
That's right.
Trigger was this year, wasn't it?
That's for sure.
It all happened so fast.
I've done so many things.
First time abroad.
All the time.
On location.
I wonder how many days we spent there.
Three days?
I don't know.
Well... a lot of places.
About four weeks.
I felt like I'd been there.
We were there from morning till night.
What did you do in May and June?
I really don't remember.
From the front page, from this year.
You've done a lot.
You've been to a lot of places. You've been a lot of places.
I've noticed.
This year?
Trigger.
Wow.
Do the iconoid thing.
And put on the back dance.
What a surprise!
The moment I saw Satori
I didn't think so.
Never mind.
I want to see him play his own songs.
It'll be fun, right?
Shuffle?
It's so much fun.
There were a lot of stages this year.
That's right.
There were stands and stuff.
There was a stand.
The sub-stage.
Side?
Yeah, on the side.
It was like a DJ booth.
Sana was so cool! Sana was so cool!
Sana.
What was that?
DJ Sana
That's right.
I don't know...
I'm laughing because it's so great... like Lisa...
She was the perfect DJ.
It really was.
Where did I start?
Do you want to put more Thai in there?
I'd love to put in some more ties.
I'd love some Thai.
Ties.
Put a lot of Thai in there.
Tie first.
Everyone else has already put theirs in.
No more cacos!
It's a Thai party!
Thai party!
Oh, he's alive.
Hey.
I don't think he's alive.
What do you think? What do you think?
I'd like to meet with a fan every week or so.
And by weekly, I mean for a shorter period of time.
You met with them? I mean, really.
There were a lot of events.
The hottest stage since your debut.
That's right, that's right.
I remember how nervous I was.
I was really nervous.
I miss it.
It's nice to be outdoors.
Fescue.
In the summer.
It's so hot.
We had fall, and it was great.
It's in the air.
What was I doing?
Oh, that.
It's our 6th anniversary.
It was in September.
I'd love to see some friends.
Yeah, yeah.
I think there was a lot of filming.
Filming and stuff.
There was a lot of filming.
A lot of secrets. A lot of secrets
Where do you want to go for your first love?
I always wanted to go to America.
I've always wanted to go to America.
I think you're right.
I want to go to Europe once.
I like it here.
I like going abroad.
I want to go to various places in Japan, too.
I'm sure.
I'm going to Hyogo for the first time.
Yes, it is.
Hyogo.
My first time.
I'm really looking forward to Hyogo.
I'm looking forward to it too.
Takarazuka.
Takarazuka
I'm going on a junior high school trip.
Hyogo?
Yeah.
Like Chinatown.
There is, isn't there?
I went there. I've been there.
Went there.
I've eaten and walked around.
Can we go sightseeing?
I wonder if I can
Style
Please
Yes, please.
I'll go!
Gluttony
It's a gluttony party.
I'm gonna put everything in.
I'll put this in too.
So much food!
Oh, my God.
Now that everyone's almost done eating...
I'd like to talk about our ambitions for next year.
Oh, I've said it a million times.
Next year's resolutions?
Six years already.
November and December... the singing show.
That's right.
I've done more shows than I've ever done in my life.
I'd like to do more. More.
Yes, I do.
If I could be on more singing shows.
Yeah, yeah.
That would be great.
I'd be happy.
I'd like people to know me better.
Next year, we're going to start with the tour.
So I'm really looking forward to meeting people in Kobe that I've never been to.
I'm really looking forward to meeting them.
It's your first time, right?
Yes, it's my first arena tour.
I want to make a lot of memories.
I'm looking forward to making lots of memories.
I'm sure you will.
Yes, I do.
We're almost at 7.
How many weeks?
and so on.
I'm always looking for new collaborations to show you.
I want to do my best
I'd like to do my best
I would be very happy if we could have more and more new fans
I would be very happy And I'm glad
And the people who like us now.
I'm sure you'll love it even more.
And this tour
Love
It's like a theme of love.
more and more and more
I don't know, everything.
Singing, dancing, talking
I hope I can do it.
I'll do my best.
Next year, I'd like to have more
I hope to collaborate with
I hope that many people
I think it would be great if people of all ages
So that people will like it.
I'll do my best.
Next year, I'll be a woman of the year.
No, you're wrong.
First born in Japan.
I'll be 20 next year.
What?
I'm turning 20. I'm turning 20.
What? Wait a minute.
I'm suddenly nervous.
Oh, no.
Teenage years.
Last year.
Last teenager.
I'm going to enjoy my last teen year to the fullest.
I want to make it a year with no regrets.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have a lot of fun together!
The weather is bad
Let's call it a night.
See you soon!
Ikarame bar New Year's party!
What?
That doesn't sound like a birthday party.
It's a New Year's Eve party.
How was it, guys?
Did you have fun?
It was fun.
It's the first time I've ever had a big New Year's party.
I can eat a lot!
It's so smooth and silky. It's so silky smooth.
This is what it looked like six years ago.
The four of us ate the whole thing.
It was so good.
It was delicious.
This year is already over.
We will all work together again next year
We will do our best again next year.
We look forward to your continued support next year.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your support this year.
See you soon!
Bye bye!